babysupermall.com 2006-04-05

# BabySuperMall.com - Privacy Policy

**Help Page:**  1 2 3 4  **5**  6  Prev  Next  [Close Window]()

### Table of Contents

> **Information We Collect  
>  Use of Cookies  
>  How We Use Information  
>  Information Sharing  
>  Links to Other Sites  
>  Security and Encryption  
>  Changing Personal Information  
>  Privacy Statement Changes  
>  Contacting the Web Site  
>  Privacy Policy & Terms of Use  
>  **  
> 

Your privacy is very important to us. We created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: http://BabySuperMall.com

### Information We Collect

We collect two types of information from you: information you submit to us and data our site gathers automatically. 

**1.  Information You Submit to Us:**  
Everyone is welcome to browse our site and there is no requirement to purchase anything at any time. If you decide to make a purchase, we will gather several pieces of information from you during the checkout process. 

Our order form uses required and non required fields. We require only the most basic contact information needed to process your payment and properly ship your order, such as name, address, phone number, and e-mail address and payment information. You may choose to not submit payment information online if this makes you uncomfortable. Simply fill out the basic information on the order form and then choose "Off-line Payment" to pay by phone, mail, or fax. 

There are also non required fields on our order form that you may use to provide more data and instructions so that your order can be handled in the way you want. Some non required information would be a separate shipping address, gift wrapping information, special shipping instructions, etc. 

**2.  Information Gathered Automatically:**  
Just like most web sites, our server automatically gathers some usage information from you so that we can improve and enhance our site based on user patterns. 

As you browse our Web site, it collects log file, IP address, and other standard tracking data we use to evaluate site traffic patterns and popular areas and pages. Such information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors and is never associated with individually identifiable information that would reveal any personal information about you.   

### Use of Cookies

Cookies enable our site to return the results you expect as you move from page to page. Our site uses cookies to ensure visits are trouble free, especially if you are using our Shopping Cart. We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. 

Cookies are not able to read any information on your computer or interact with other cookies on your hard drive. 

You can turn off the cookie acceptance option in your browser settings if you do not want your browser to accept cookies. However, disabling cookie support may prevent this site from working properly as you shop.   

### How We Use Information

We may use the information you provide during the check-out process for any or all of the following: to process your payment, to process and ship your order, to send you e-mail about your order, and/or to call you on the phone if we have questions about your order. 

If you submit credit card information, we use that information to collect payment for your order which may include verifying your name, address, and phone number with your Card Issuer (this is a fraud protection measure required by the Credit Card companies). 

We may use contact information from our surveys, contests, affiliate applications, and newsletter subscriptions to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. We will always ask your permission first. You may un-subscribe at any time. Contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary.   

### Information Sharing

**BabySuperMall.com** shares some of your information with third parties that may be involved in processing your order. This is the ONLY reason we share information. 

Third parties who may be involved in processing your order include (but not limited to) Credit Card Issuing Banks and freight carriers such as UPS and USPS. Only the relevant data needed by each third party is released to them. 

**We never willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about our site visitors or customers to third parties without their permission. WE DO NOT SELL USERS' NAMES OR E-MAIL ADDRESSES TO OTHER COMPANIES. We may provide individually identifiable information to third parties in any case where it is required by law.**

Any display ads or links to external sites shown on our site may collect user information if you click or follow their ads. We do not control any data collected voluntarily or involuntarily through these ads. Investigate the privacy policies of any advertised site if you have concerns about its collection and use of user information.   

### Links to Other Sites

This site may contain external links to other web sites, such as (but not limited to) suppliers' sites and advertisers' sites. **BabySuperMall.com** has no control over the content of third party sites and is not responsible for any information contained on these sites, nor is **BabySuperMall.com** responsible for the privacy policies of those sites and the information they may gather expressly or automatically.   

### Security and Encryption

**BabySuperMall.com** uses industry standard measures to safeguard your individually identifiable information. This includes SSL encryption and a secure server to encrypt your sensitive credit card information transmitted from your browser to our server.   

### Changing Personal Information

You have the option of correcting, updating, and modifying your individually identifiable customer information at any time and as often as you need to. To change your personal information simply e-mail or call us. 

  1. E-mail [service@BabySuperMall.com](mailto:service@BabySuperMall.com)
  2. Or, call toll free (Monday - Friday, 8:45am - 4:45pm CST) 1-888-276-6654 

### Privacy Statement Changes

Changes in this privacy statement are posted on this page (http://babysupermall.comPrivacy.html). Please check the bottom of this page for the last revision date. 

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact our Corporate Offices or call 1-847-468-6031.   

### Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

This Privacy Policy co-exists with our Terms of Use policy and together both policies govern the general practices of this site. We encourage all of our users to familiarize themselves with both statements.   

**Last revised:   January 8, 2003**

**Help Page:**  1 2 3 4

 **5**  6  Prev  Next  [Close Window]()
